Live like there's no tomorrow
Palm Springs is a comedy, romance, science
fiction film directed by Max Barbakow.
When carefree Nyles and reluctant maid of honor Sarah have a chance encounter at a Palm Springs wedding, things
get complicated when they find themselves unable to escape the venue, themselves, or each other.
Nyles, played by Andy Samberg.
Sarah, played by Cristin Milioti.
Roy, played by J.K. Simmons.
Howard, played by Peter Gallagher.
Misty, played by Meredith Hagner.
Tala, played by Camila Mendes.
Palm Springs is a 2020 American science fiction romantic comedy film directed by Max Barbakow (in his feature
directorial debut) from a screenplay by Andy Siara, based on a story by Barbakow and Siara.
Starring Andy Samberg (who also produced the film), Cristin Milioti, and J.
Simmons, it focuses on two strangers who meet at a wedding in Palm
Springs only to find themselves stuck in a time loop.
Palm Springs premiered at the 2020 Sundance Film Festival on January 26, and it was
simultaneously released on Hulu and in select theaters by Neon on July 10, 2020.
The film received critical acclaim for its use of
the concept and cast performances.
At the 78th Golden Globe Awards, it earned two nominations: Best Motion Picture – Musical or
Comedy and Best Actor in a Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy for Samberg.
Among other accolades, it won Best Comedy at the 26th Critics' Choice Awards.
The film explores themes of alcohol, cave, time
travel, earthquake, swimming pool.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.